[
     {
      "question": "What is the median of these numbers:<br> [31, 32, 33, 34, 35, 36, 131]?",
      "correctAnswer": "34",
      "options": [
        "33",
        "34",
        "35",
        "36"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the median of these numbers:<br> [32, 33, 34, 35, 36, 37, 132]?",
      "correctAnswer": "35",
      "options": [
        "34",
        "35",
        "36",
        "37"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the median of these numbers:<br> [33, 34, 35, 36, 37, 38, 133]?",
      "correctAnswer": "36",
      "options": [
        "35",
        "36",
        "37",
        "38"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the median of these numbers:<br> [34, 35, 36, 37, 38, 39, 134]?",
      "correctAnswer": "37",
      "options": [
        "36",
        "37",
        "38",
        "39"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the median of these numbers:<br> [35, 36, 37, 38, 39, 40, 135]?",
      "correctAnswer": "38",
      "options": [
        "37",
        "38",
        "39",
        "40"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the median of these numbers:<br> [36, 37, 38, 39, 40, 41, 136]?",
      "correctAnswer": "39",
      "options": [
        "38",
        "39",
        "40",
        "41"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the median of these numbers:<br> [37, 38, 39, 40, 41, 42, 137]?",
      "correctAnswer": "40",
      "options": [
        "39",
        "40",
        "41",
        "42"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the median of these numbers:<br> [38, 39, 40, 41, 42, 43, 138]?",
      "correctAnswer": "41",
      "options": [
        "40",
        "41",
        "42",
        "43"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the median of these numbers:<br> [39, 40, 41, 42, 43, 44, 139]?",
      "correctAnswer": "42",
      "options": [
        "41",
        "42",
        "43",
        "44"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the median of these numbers:<br> [40, 41, 42, 43, 44, 45, 46]?",
      "correctAnswer": "43",
      "options": [
        "42",
        "43",
        "44",
        "45"
      ]
    }
]